Naas, Bernard G. and Carmelita Sakr Collection of Documents and Manuscript for "American Labor Union Periodicals" /3039
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Bernard G. Naas and Carmelita Sakr Collection of Documents and Manuscript for "American Labor Union Periodicals"
1891-1955
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Naas, Bernard G.
Sakr, Carmelita S.
/3039
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Bibliographies, publications (documents).
Includes the Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals from 1936 to 1954, along with correspondence with various university library throughout the US.
3074604
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 21, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3046: Leonard P. Adams Papers /4073: James O. Morris Office Files /4297: ILR School Biography Files
Labor unions -- United States -- Periodicals -- Bibliography; Naas, Bernard G.; Sakr, Carmelita S.
3074604
- Minnesota University of Nelson, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- New York Public Library OKO, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- University of North Carolina Mrs. Guelda von Beckerarth, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Ohio State University Shartle, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Princeton University Baker, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Queens University Gray, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Rutgers University Berman, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- U.S. Dept. of Labor Library Brickett, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Washington, University of Larrowe, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Wisconsin Wilcox, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Union List, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Michigan, University of Scanlon, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Holdings of U.S. Labor Union Periodicals (117 titles), 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Notecards
- Notecards (Boxed), 1900-1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Labor Notecards F-Z (Boxed), 1900-1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Labor Notecards A-E, 1900-1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1936-1938 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Preface, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- (Misc.) (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1942-1954 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1938-1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- California, University of (Los Angeles) Thomason, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Stanford University Greisinger, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- California, University of (Berkeley), 1954 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- California Institute of Technology Burroughs Lockett CPT, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Canada. Dept. of Labor Library Wilson, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Chicago, University of Harper ICU, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Cornell University NYSSILR Miller NIC-I, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Denver, University of Dudack CoDu, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Columbia University Bogardus, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Harvard University Garvey, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Illinois, University of McCoy, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- MdBJ Johns Hopkins University Mr. J. Louis Kuethe, Asst. Lib., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology Klingenhagen MCM, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Union List of American Labor Union Periodicals, 1892-1947 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Book 1 Actors to Carriage, 1902-1950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Book 2 Catholic to Glass, 1916-1950 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Book 3 Glass to Lumber, 1909-1953 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Book 4 Lumber to Natural Labor Union, 1913-1953 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Book 5 Needle to Retail, 1891-1950 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Book 6 Retail to Tailors National, 1927-1951 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Book 7 Tailors to, 1912-1952 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Notebook CU, 1898-1950 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Notebook CU, 1917-1955 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Union List Union Periodicals, 1936-1954 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Union List of American Labor Periodicals, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 25)